const quizData = [
  {
    question: "Who started reggae music in Jamaica?",
    options: ["Bob Marley", "Toots and the Maytals", "Lee Perry", "Shaggy"],
    correctAnswer: "Toots and the Maytals",
    subquestion: {
      question: "In 1968, the band Toots and the Maytals recorded their first Reggae song titled?",
      options: ["Give me Hope", "Jah live", "54-46 was my Number", "Buffalo soldier"],
      correctAnswer: "54-46  was my Number"
    }
  },

  {
    question: "Which artist is referred to as the crown prince of Reggae?",
    options: ["Bob Marley", "Dennis Brown", "Garnett Silk", "Culture"],
    correctAnswer: "Dennis Brown"
  },
  
  {
    question: "Who is referred to as the 'King of Reggae'?",
    options: ["Toots and the Maytals", "Lee Perry", "Bob Marley", "Shaggy"],
    correctAnswer: "Bob Marley"
  },

  {
    question: "Which Bob Marley song includes the lyrics: \"No bullet can stop us now, we neither beg nor we won't bow.\"",
    options: ["Exodus", "Waiting in Vain", "Three Little Birds", "Jamming"],
    correctAnswer: "Jamming"
  },

  {
    question: "What year did Reggae Legend Bob Marley pass away?",
    options: ["1979", "1981", "1983", "1985"],
    correctAnswer: "1981"
  },

  {
    question: "Which reggae artist is known for the song Night Nurse?",
    options: ["Peter Tosh", "Jimmy Cliff", "Gregory Isaac's", "Bob Marley"],
    correctAnswer: "Gregory Isaac's"
  },

  {
    question: "In which Jamaican parish did reggae originate?",
    options: ["Trelawny", "St. Ann", "St. Elizabeth", "Westmoreland"],
    correctAnswer: "St. Ann"
  },

  {
    question: "Which reggae artist fought through music for the freedom of southafrica?",
    options: ["Bob Marley", "Alpha Blondy", "Lucky Dube", "Althea and DonnaJohn Holt"],
    correctAnswer: "Lucky Dube"
  },

  {
    question: "Here i come is a big worldwide Reggae song from singer?",
    options: ["Junior Murvin", "Barrington Levy", "Gregory Isaacs", "Steel Pulse"],
    correctAnswer: "Barrington Levy",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is considered the 'Queen of Reggae'?",
    options: ["Marcia Griffiths", "Queen Ifrica", "Sister Nancy", "Althea and Donna"],
    correctAnswer: "Marcia Griffiths",
    subquestion: [
      {
        question: "In which female reggae group did Marcia Griffiths originally gain fame?",
        options: ["I-Threes", "The Melodians", "The Pioneers", "The Soulettes"],
        correctAnswer: "The Soulettes"
      },
      {
        question: "Marcia Griffiths collaborated with Bob Marley on the duet ______.",
        options: ["One Love", "No Woman, No Cry", "The Electric Slide", "Three Little Birds"],
        correctAnswer: "No Woman, No Cry"
      }
    ]
  },
];


  




  
